{"SatVocab100FREE" : [{"Question":"Abhor","Answer":"hate"},
{"Question":"Bigot","Answer":"narrow-minded, prejudiced person"},
{"Question":"Counterfeit","Answer":"fake; false"},
{"Question":"Enfranchise","Answer":"give voting rights"},
{"Question":"Hamper","Answer":"hinder; obstruct"},
{"Question":"Kindle","Answer":"to start a fire"},
{"Question":"Noxious","Answer":"harmful; poisonous; lethal"},
{"Question":"Placid","Answer":"calm; peaceful"},
{"Question":"Remuneration","Answer":"payment for work done"},
{"Question":"Talisman","Answer":"lucky charm"},
{"Question":"Abrasive","Answer":"rough; coarse; harsh"},
{"Question":"Bilk","Answer":"cheat; defraud"},
{"Question":"Covert","Answer":"hidden; undercover"},
{"Question":"Engender","Answer":"cause"},
{"Question":"Hangar","Answer":"storage area (like garage) for a plane"},
{"Question":"Knotty","Answer":"complex; difficult to solve"},
{"Question":"Nuance","Answer":"something subtle; a fine shade of meaning"},
{"Question":"Plagiarism","Answer":"taking credit for someone else's writing or ideas"},
{"Question":"Renown","Answer":"fame"},
{"Question":"Tangent","Answer":"going off the main subject"},
{"Question":"Abasement","Answer":"humiliation; degradation"},
{"Question":"Billowing","Answer":"swelling; fluttering; waving"},
{"Question":"Cower","Answer":"recoil in fear or servility; shrink away from"},
{"Question":"Enhance","Answer":"improve; make better or clearer"},
{"Question":"Harangue","Answer":"noisy, attacking speech"},
{"Question":"Labyrinth","Answer":"a maze"},
{"Question":"Nullify","Answer":"to counter; make unimportant"},
{"Question":"Plaintiff","Answer":"petitioner (in court of law)"},
{"Question":"Replete","Answer":"full"},
{"Question":"Tangible","Answer":"can be touched"},
{"Question":"Abrogate","Answer":"cancel; deny; repeal"},
{"Question":"Blasphemy","Answer":"speech which offends religious sentiments"},
{"Question":"Credible","Answer":"believable"},
{"Question":"Enigma","Answer":"puzzle; mystery"},
{"Question":"Harbingers","Answer":"indicators; bringers of warnings"},
{"Question":"Labyrinthine","Answer":"complicated; highly convoluted"},
{"Question":"Nuzzle","Answer":"cuddle; snuggle"},
{"Question":"Plaudit","Answer":"statement giving strong praise"},
{"Question":"Reprehensible","Answer":"shameful; very bad"},
{"Question":"Tardy","Answer":"slow; late; overdue; delayed"},
{"Question":"Absolution","Answer":"forgiveness; pardon; release"},
{"Question":"Blatant","Answer":"obvious"},
{"Question":"Creditable","Answer":"praiseworthy"},
{"Question":"Ensconce","Answer":"establish firmly in a position"},
{"Question":"Hasten","Answer":"hurry; accelerate; rush"},
{"Question":"Laceration","Answer":"a cut"},
{"Question":"Obdurate","Answer":"stubborn"},
{"Question":"Plausible","Answer":"can be believed; reasonable"},
{"Question":"Reprieve","Answer":"a respite; postponement of a sentence"},
{"Question":"Tawdry","Answer":"of little value; gaudy"},
{"Question":"Abstain","Answer":"desist; go without; withdraw"},
{"Question":"Blighted","Answer":"damaged; destroyed; ruined"},
{"Question":"Credulous","Answer":"gullible; ready to believe anything"},
{"Question":"Enshroud","Answer":"cover"},
{"Question":"Haughtiness","Answer":"arrogance; pride"},
{"Question":"Lachrymose","Answer":"tearful; sad"},
{"Question":"Obfuscate","Answer":"deliberately make something difficult to understand"},
{"Question":"Plethora","Answer":"an excess"},
{"Question":"Repudiate","Answer":"shun; eschew"},
{"Question":"Tedium","Answer":"boredom"},
{"Question":"Abstemious","Answer":"self denying; refraining from indulging"},
{"Question":"Blithe","Answer":"free-spirited; carefree"},
{"Question":"Crepuscular","Answer":"active at dawn and dusk"},
{"Question":"Enunciation","Answer":"clear pronunciation; accent; articulation"},
{"Question":"Headstrong","Answer":"stubborn; willful"},
{"Question":"Lackluster","Answer":"dull; monotonous; bland"},
{"Question":"Objective","Answer":"unbiased; not subjective"},
{"Question":"Pliable","Answer":"flexible; not stubborn"},
{"Question":"Rescind","Answer":"retract; repeal"},
{"Question":"Temper","Answer":"to moderate; soften"},
{"Question":"Abstruse","Answer":"difficult to understand; obscure"},
{"Question":"Blunderbuss","Answer":"1. ancient weapon (type of gun); 2. a clumsy person"},
{"Question":"Cringe","Answer":"recoil; flinch; shy away"},
{"Question":"Envenom","Answer":"to cause bitterness and bad feeling"},
{"Question":"Hedonism","Answer":"self indulgence; pleasure-seeking"},
{"Question":"Laconic","Answer":"using few words; brief; to the point"},
{"Question":"Oblique","Answer":"indirect; slanting"},
{"Question":"Plumage","Answer":"feathers of a bird"},
{"Question":"Resignation","Answer":"acceptance of fate"},
{"Question":"Tenacious","Answer":"stubborn; resolute; holding firm to a purpose"},
{"Question":"Accolade","Answer":"tribute; honor; praise"},
{"Question":"Bolster","Answer":"support; prop up"},
{"Question":"Cryptic","Answer":"puzzling; enigmatic"},
{"Question":"Ephemeral","Answer":"short-lived"},
{"Question":"Hedonist","Answer":"a pleasure seeker"},
{"Question":"Lamentation","Answer":"expression of regret or sorrow"},
{"Question":"Obliterate","Answer":"destroy; demolish; eradicate"},
{"Question":"Plummet","Answer":"fall suddenly and steeply"},
{"Question":"Resolution","Answer":"determination"},
{"Question":"Tentative","Answer":"not certain"},
{"Question":"Acquiesce","Answer":"to agree to; give in to"},
{"Question":"Bombast","Answer":"arrogant, pompous language"},
{"Question":"Curtail","Answer":"cut short"},
{"Question":"Epicure","Answer":"someone who appreciates good food and drink"},
{"Question":"Heed","Answer":"listen to"},
{"Question":"Lampoon","Answer":"ridicule; spoof"},
{"Question":"Oblivious","Answer":"totally unaware"},
{"Question":"Podium","Answer":"raised platform"},
{"Question":"Resonant","Answer":"echoing"},
{"Question":"Tenuous","Answer":"flimsy; not solid"}]
}